You did a wonderful job. Wonderful.
You did it. You did it!
To continue, you've listened to a long and
complex case, murder in the first degree.
Premeditated murder is the most serious
charge tried in our criminal courts.
You've listened to the testimony, had the
law interpreted as it applies in this case.
It's now your duty to sit down and try
and separate the facts from the fancy.
One man is dead.
Another man's life is at stake.
If there's a reasonable doubt in your
minds as to the guilt of the accused -
a reasonable doubt-then you must
bring me a verdict of not guilty.
If there's no reasonable doubt,
then you must, in good conscience,
find the accused guilty.
However you decide,
your verdict must be unanimous.
In the event that
you find the accused guilty,
the bench will not entertain
a recommendation for mercy.
The death sentence is mandatory
in this case.
You are faced with a grave responsibility.
Thank you, gentlemen.
The alternate jurors are excused.
The jury will now retire.
- Wanna piece of gum?
- No, thanks.
This thing isn't movin'.
- I'll give you a hand.
- That's it.
You know somethin'? I called
the Weather Bureau this morning.
This is gonna be
the hottest day of the year.
You'd think they'd air-condition this place.
- What is your name, sir?
- Oh, it's... that one. Yeah.
Thank you very much.
OK, gentlemen. Everybody's here.
Now, if there's anything you want,
I'll be right outside the door. Just knock.
Good morning.
I never knew they locked the door.
Sure they lock the door.
What'd you think?
I don't know. It just never occurred to me.
- What's that for?
- I thought we might wanna vote by ballot.
Great idea. Maybe we can
get him elected senator.
- How'd you like it?
- I don't know. It was pretty interesting.
- Yeah? I almost fell asleep.
- I mean, I've never been on a jury before.
No? I've sat on many juries.
Those lawyers talk and talk, even when
it's an open-and-shut case like this one.
- Ever hear so much talk about nothin'?
- I guess they're entitled.
They're entitled. It's the system, but...
if you ask me, I'd slap those tough kids
down before they start any trouble.
It saves a lot of time and money.
Let's get started.
Yeah. We've probably all
got things to do here.
We can start with a five-minute break.
One gentleman is in the bathroom.
Are... we gonna sit in order?
Gee, I don't know. I guess so.
- Buddy